<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Direct Charity</title>
    <link>https://dkotik.github.io/direct-charity/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Direct Charity</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://dkotik.github.io/direct-charity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prepare</title>
      <link>https://dkotik.github.io/direct-charity/transfers/ukraine/paypal-xoom-monobank/prepare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dkotik.github.io/direct-charity/transfers/ukraine/paypal-xoom-monobank/prepare/</guid>
      <description>Sending using Xoom (a PayPal company), and Monobank This method enables instant transfers that does not require visiting a physical bank. The first transfer will take about 30 minutes to complete. Subsequent transfers to the same person take 1-2 minutes. The transfer fees are low. You can send no more than $3,000 per month per recipient.
Once in Europe, the funds can be collected using &amp;ldquo;RIA&amp;rdquo; payment system in most banks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Receive</title>
      <link>https://dkotik.github.io/direct-charity/transfers/ukraine/paypal-xoom-monobank/receive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dkotik.github.io/direct-charity/transfers/ukraine/paypal-xoom-monobank/receive/</guid>
      <description>Receive Previous step: Send Funds Подготовка Для пересылки в долларах необходимо открыть валютную карту в приложении Монобанка. Эта карта виртуальная. Не нужно никуда идти в банковское отделение, фотографировать и загружать фото паспорта, открывается бесплатно в приложении. Передайте другу ваши данные. Они все должны быть набраны латинскими буквами:
Имя и Фамилия латинскими буквами как на банковской карте номер мобильного телефона адрес проживания имейл, если хотите получать оповещения Получение В верхней части приложения выберите опцию карты: Нажмите на кнопку &amp;ldquo;Відкрити карту або ФОП&amp;rdquo; Выберите карту в $ долларах, и затем подтвердите ваш выбор и пользовательское соглашение.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Send</title>
      <link>https://dkotik.github.io/direct-charity/transfers/ukraine/paypal-xoom-monobank/send/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dkotik.github.io/direct-charity/transfers/ukraine/paypal-xoom-monobank/send/</guid>
      <description>Send Previous step: Collect Information Add a new recipient Ensure that the correct country is selected. Add a new recipient. Fill in all the information about them collected in the previous step.
Select currency &amp;ldquo;USD&amp;rdquo; and the amount to send. It is possible to use other currencies, but it may complicate some steps. USD is better for cross-border solvency and storage.
Send funds Login into Xoom account . Select &amp;ldquo;Quick Send&amp;rdquo; from Xoom home page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ship Books using Meest</title>
      <link>https://dkotik.github.io/direct-charity/shipping/meest/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dkotik.github.io/direct-charity/shipping/meest/books/</guid>
      <description>Ship Books Using Meest 1. Pack the box Use box size 16x16x16 inches aiming for ~65 pounds weight. Heavier items like books will pack to ~85% of the total available volume. Tape the outside bottom of the box generously covering the middle seam completely. Put a layer or two of cardboard on the inside bottom of the box. This greatly reduces the chance that the bottom may spill during delivery. Count the number of books as you place them inside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ship Humanitarian Aid to Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://dkotik.github.io/direct-charity/shipping/meest/over200lbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dkotik.github.io/direct-charity/shipping/meest/over200lbs/</guid>
      <description>Ship Humanitarian Aid to Ukraine using Meest 1. Collect items Warm children&amp;rsquo;s clothing are frequently requested items. Some ideas:
$15 pack of 2x double layered hats $20 set of cotton baby socks $30 pack of Two 55% Cotton girl sweater Used clothes are totally welcome. Raid your local Good Will! Please, select things of good quality. Natural fibers, like wool and cotton, have better thermal qualities than synthetic fibers, like polyester or nylon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ship Parcel to Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://dkotik.github.io/direct-charity/shipping/meest/parcel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dkotik.github.io/direct-charity/shipping/meest/parcel/</guid>
      <description>Ship Parcel to Ukraine using Meest 1. Collect items Warm children&amp;rsquo;s clothing are frequently requested items. Some ideas:
$15 pack of 2x double layered hats $20 set of cotton baby socks $30 pack of Two 55% Cotton girl sweater Used clothes are totally welcome. Raid your local Good Will! Please, select things of good quality. Natural fibers, like wool and cotton, have better thermal qualities than synthetic fibers, like polyester or nylon.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
